I cannot believe you're going to tell on me.
真不敢相信，你们居然打算告发我。
You're like a pair of horrible old women.
你们俩就像一对老巫婆。
What did she say?
他说什么？
She said we're like horrible old women.
他说我们像老巫婆。
She didn't!
不是吧！
Hey guys! So,
你们好啊，伙计们！
what do you wanna tell me?
找我有事吗？
Well, it's like this...
有点事，是这样的…
Look at you! My CET 4 team！
看看你们！我的四级团队！
Yeah.
对
Team players each and every one of you.
你们每个人都是团队的一员.
oh Yeah, well,what she... er...
没错，但她…
There's no room for people on my team who can't act like a team!
在我这儿没有团队精神可不行！
Excuse me. Hello? What?
抱歉。喂？什么？
Well if you can't work as a team, you're fired!
要是你们不能像团队一样工作,就给我走人！
Everyone of you! That's it,you heard me,fired!
就是那样，你没听错，你们被解雇了！
Get your things and go!
拿着你的东西走人！
Hello, Security?
喂，保卫科吗？
Everyone on floor 4 is fired.
四楼的人都被炒了.
Escort them from the premises as soon as possible.
把他们送出大楼.
And if you can't work as a team, you're all fired too!
记住你们是个团队，如果没有团队精神你们也给我走人！
Done!
道恩！
Get onto recruitment.
找人事部
Tell them to look for a security team that can act as a team.
让他们招一组有团队精神的保安队.
They may have to escort the old security team from the building,
让他们把现在的保安队轰出去，
for not acting like a team!
他们没有团队精神！
Team! Team! Team!Team! Team! Team!
团队! 团队! 团队! 团队...
I even love saying the word "Team".
我特喜欢说这个词.
So what do you wanna tell me?
话说你们来找我什么事？
Well, it's just not working out.
那个，我们之间合不来。
He's joking!
他在开玩笑呢！
But you said...It’s not working out!
但是你说… 合不来？
No! We are getting on like a big house on fire!
啊没有！没有！我们之间好着呢，感情火热的像着火的房子！
My ears‘ getting hot!
我的耳朵好烫！
You know what? We should leave now,
我们该走了,
you're a busy man and we've taken far too much of your time.Ok,
因为你是个大忙人，我们已经占用你很多时间了。
Chloe, could you get the door for me there?
Chloe，你能帮我开一下门吗？
Yes,I will.
当然啦.
So,why did you come here in the first place?
那你们一开始来这儿是干嘛？
We, as a new team,
我们作为一个新团队，
we just wanna come by and say
就想给你过来说，
that we are so pleased to meet each other and become a new team,
我们很开心能遇到彼此并成为团队，
okay so, thank you very much, and bye, thank you! Bye!
非常感谢您，再见，谢谢！
Team！Yeah！
团队！耶！
I mean, what good are you?
我说，你到底会什么？
You obviously don't know anything about CET 4.
很明显你对四级一窍不通。
No, but...OK. I can learn. I mean,
我是不懂，可...没关系，我可以学嘛,
for example,
比如，
Max,you could take me through what you're doing right now.
Max,你可以简单说下你在做什么吗。
I'd be delighted!
非常乐意!
I see... Oh no, I'm lying again!
原来如此...天啊，我又撒谎了！
I didn’t understand any of that!
我一点都没听懂！
I don't know anything about CET,
我对四级或教学一窍不通，
I'm absolutely useless to you guys.
对你们丝毫无用处，
I might as well pack up and go home.
我还是收拾东西回家算了。
Hi! Is Joe around?
你好，Joe在吗？
Hello there! Are you lost?
你好啊，小姑娘！你迷路了吗？
How can I help you? I'm Joe.
要我带你回家吗？我就是Joe。
You kicked my kid out of here?
你把我孩子赶出去了吗？
Well how dare you! !
胆子够大啊！
Not the face! !
别打脸！
Yeah well,
是嘛，
maybe this will teach you to treat people with a little bit of respect!
或许这能教教你，对人要有点儿礼貌！
Is it certainly 'cos I spoke on the phone earlier with your daughter?
真是因为之前的那通电话吗？
Oh my god! Are those Air Jordan’s?
我的天呐！这鞋是AJ的吗？
Oh, yes.
哦，是的。
They are gorgeous! Were they expensive?
太好看了！是不是很贵啊？
No, no no! Got them in a sale.
不不不！打折时买的。
Oh God! Clever you!
天啊，你真聪明！
I wish I got a bargain like you.
我从没赶上过这么值的东西。
Well, I should take you shopping.
没事，下次我带你去。
That would be fantastic.
行啊，太好了。
Oh, I will give you a call.
哦！我会给你打电话的。
Nice to meet you! Take care!
很高兴见到你！保重！
Chairman! Wow!
哇！你太厉害了！
You just diffuse that entire situation!
整个危机局势让你通通化解了！
What situation?
什么危机局势？
Oh oh, that...yeah! Oh my God,
哦，你说那个啊... 没错。
does that happen a lot?
天啊，这种事常发生吗？
They're fairly regular, the beatings,
这种殴打规律出现，
Yes,I'd say we're on a biweekly beatings.
没错,我们每两周挨一次揍。
Ah, it's not all that bad!
没你说的那么惨啦！
Ah, come on! It's really bad.
算了吧，就是这么惨。
Maybe I could help with this,
这种事我也许能帮上忙
you know. I mean,
恩
I'm a people person,
我是善于交际的人，
and people like you need a person to deal with people,
而你们这种类型的人需要找个人帮忙跟他人打交道，
a people person like me.
找一个像我这样的善于交际的人。
Oh my God! Ideas are coming!
哦老天！有主意了！
Things are happening here!
大脑开动了！
Ok, Ok. What would you say,
好的好的。你们看这样如何，
yeah. If I told you that I had a plan to raise your profile by 100%.
如果我有个计划，可以把你们的形象提升一倍。
What would you say?
你们看怎样？
We can start from colleagues from other departments.
可以从其他部门的同事开始。
It can't be done! You're crazy!
那不可能！你疯了！
What would you say Joe?
你觉得呢Joe？
Oh Joe passed out!
Joe晕倒了！
I need a felttip pen, and some paper.
好吧，我需要一支笔和几张纸。